[Music]
[Applause]
part
two number seven how much longer do you
need on this
project a about 10 pages long B roughly
half an hour C in my office
soon number eight why hasn't anyone
responded to that
complaint a that's the response she gave
us B yes it looks a bit plain to me c I
thought Ted already handled
it number nine do you want me to see if
the item is still in stock a I would
appreciate that a lot B I don't have
stock in that company C this is the item
that I purched
number 10 the picnic has been postponed
until next week hasn't it a sometime
last Friday B that's what I heard C I'm
going to the
picnic number 11 you'd better be on your
best behavior at the
meeting a he's behaving prop properly B
that's the best product C I promise to
do
that number 12 nobody can remember Miss
carlile's phone number right a you
should ask Jane for it B she called a
while ago C no I'm not on the
phone number 13
where is the nearest gas station in this
neighborhood a I'll fill up the car
later today B we're in the cold water
neighborhood C there's one right down
the
street number
14 what time should we expect Miss
Carter to
arrive a on Monday or Tuesday B sometime
after 6 C
around 40 minutes
ago number 15 I believe you ought to see
a doctor about that cough a that's what
my husband said B he's been coughing all
day C no I don't want any
coffee number 16 who should we send on
the business trip to Tokyo
a about 2 weeks from now B to negotiate
a new contract C how about Mark or
Anna number
17 can you give me directions to the
wishbone
Cafe a yes this is the map you asked for
B you'll love the selection of T's there
C sorry but I've never heard of it
number
18 which of these three proposals are we
thinking of
accepting a yes there are three of them
B probably the second one C we will
accept the offer
tomorrow number
19 will Martin conduct the interviews or
is JN doing them a actually Peter will
be doing them B Martin and John are
co-workers C yes that's
correct number 20 there appears to be a
problem with your cause
engine a thanks for fixing it for me B
what exactly is wrong with it C how much
do I owe you for it
number
21 I can't recall where Miss Hamilton's
office is
located a she's in Mr Wilkins office now
B it's in the building by the sultan
theater C no I haven't located her
yet number
22 the agenda for the staff meeting is
already settled isn't it a not to the
best of my knowledge B yes Jeff is a
member of the staff here C I settled the
problem this
morning number
23 how often does the subway come to
this
station a five or six times an hour B on
the number three line C go out exit
number
nine no number 24 would you prefer
taking the train or flying to the
conference a yes that's a good idea B we
flew there last week C either is fine
with
me number
25 did you remember to turn off the
lights before you left a yes I remember
what they look like B oh no I totally
forgot C no I haven't left the office
yet number
26 the interviews won't begin until this
Friday will they a I believe that's
correct B Fred's going to interview then
C Friday's a busy day for
her number 27 would you mind picking up
a sandwich from the deli for me a they
are delighted to see you B sure I can
share my lunch with you c not at all
what would you
like number
28 I suggest calling the customer
service hotline
immediately a yes you can borrow my
telephone B I'm expecting to get good
service C do you know the telephone
number number
29 what do I need to do to open a new
bank account here a I need two forms of
picture ID B fill out this form to
withdraw money C at the First National
Bank
BR number 30 shouldn't we reserve a car
for our trip to Los
Angeles a no I haven't reserved a car
yet B we could just take public
transportation C on the morning of the
30th number
31 we need to get in touch with the
caterer regarding the event a I'll
instruct Miss Johnson to do that B
please be sure not to touch it c i
catered several meals in the
[Music]
past number seven how much longer do you
need on this
project a about 10 pages long B roughly
half an hour C in my office soon
number eight why hasn't anyone responded
to that
complaint a that's the response she gave
us B yes it looks a bit plain to me c I
thought Ted already handled
it number 9 do you want me to see if the
item is still in stock a I would appre
appreciate that a lot B I don't have
stock in that company C this is the item
that I
purchased number 10 the picnic has been
postponed until next week hasn't it a
sometime last Friday B that's what I
heard C I'm going to the picnic
number 11 you'd better be on your best
behavior at the
meeting a he's behaving properly B
that's the best product C I promise to
do
that number 12 nobody can remember Miss
carlile's phone number right a you
should ask Jane for it B she called a
while ago C
no I'm not on the
phone number
13 where is the nearest gas station in
this
neighborhood a I'll fill up the car
later today B we're in the cold water
neighborhood C there's one right down
the
street number
14 what time should we expect Miss
Carter to arrive 5 a on Monday or
Tuesday B sometime after 6 C around 40
minutes
ago number 15 I believe you ought to see
a doctor about that cough a that's what
my husband said B he's been coughing all
day C no I don't want any coffee
number 16 who should we send on the
business trip to
Tokyo a about 2 weeks from now B to
negotiate a new contract C how about
Mark or
Anna number
17 can you give me directions to the
wishbone
Cafe a yes this is the map you asked for
B you'll love the selection of T's there
C sorry but I've never heard of
it number
18 which of these three proposals are we
thinking of
accepting a yes there are three of them
B probably the second one C we will
accept the offer tomorrow
number
19 will Martin conduct the interviews or
is John doing them a actually Peter will
be doing them B Martin and John are
co-workers C yes that's
correct number 20 there appears to be a
problem with your car's
engine a thanks for fixing it for me B
what exactly is wrong with it C how much
do I owe you for
it number
21 I can't recall where Miss Hamilton's
office is
located a she's in Mr Wilkins office now
B it's in the building by the sultan
theater C no I haven't located her
yet number 22
the agenda for the staff meeting is
already settled isn't it a not to the
best of my knowledge B yes Jeff is a
member of the staff here C I settled the
problem this
morning number
23 how often does the subway come to
this
station a five or six times an hour B on
the number three line C go out exit
number
nine number
24 would you prefer taking the train or
flying to the
conference a yes that's a good idea B we
flew there last week C either is fine
with
me number
25 did you remember to turn off the
lights before you left left a yes I
remember what they look like B oh no I
totally forgot C no I haven't left the
office
yet number
26 the interviews won't begin until this
Friday will they a I believe that's
correct B Fred's going to interview then
C Friday's a busy day for her
number 27 would you mind picking up a
sandwich from the deli for me a they are
delighted to see you B sure I can share
my lunch with you c not at all what
would you
like number
28 I suggest calling the customer
service hotline immediately
a yes you can borrow my telephone B I'm
expecting to get good service C do you
know the telephone
number number
29 what do I need to do to open a new
bank account here a I need two forms of
picture ID B fill out this form to
withdraw money C at the First National
Bank br
number 30 shouldn't we reserve a car for
our trip to Los
Angeles a no I haven't reserved a car
yet B we could just take public
transportation C on the morning of the
30th number 31 we need to get in touch
with the caterer regarding the event a
I'll in instruct Miss Johnson to do that
B please be sure not to touch it c i
catered several meals in the past